http://www.abney-park.org.uk/policy/

Terms Of Service
Privacy Policy:
We operate abney-park.org.uk. It is our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, abney-park.org.uk collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. abney-park.org.uk purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how abney-park.org.uk visitors use its website. From time to time, abney-park.org.uk may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
abney-park.org.uk also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on abney-park.org.uk blogs/sites. abney-park.org.uk only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to abney-park.org.uk websites choose to interact with abney-park.org.uk in ways that require abney-park.org.uk to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that abney-park.org.uk gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who wish to get in touch with us at abney-park.org.uk to provide a name and email address. abney-park.org.uk collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with abney-park.org.uk. abney-park.org.uk does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
abney-park.org.uk may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. abney-park.org.uk may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, abney-park.org.uk does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
abney-park.org.uk discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on abney-park.org.uk behalf or to provide services available at abney-park.org.uk websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organisations may be located outside of your home country; by using the abney-park.org.uk website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. abney-park.org.uk will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizsations, as described above, abney-park.org.uk discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when abney-park.org.uk believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of abney-park.org.uk, third parties or the public at large.
If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. abney-park.org.uk takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorised access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. abney-park.org.uk uses cookies to help abney-park.org.uk identify and track visitors, their usage of abney-park.org.uk website, and their website access preferences. abney-park.org.uk visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using abney-park.org.uk websites, with the drawback that certain features of abney-park.org.uk websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognise your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by abney-park.org.uk and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, abney-park.org.uk may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in abney-park.org.uk sole discretion. abney-park.org.uk encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Facebook feed
2 years ago
Abney Unearthed Tour - The Common Graves of Abney - 9th September - 2pm
Abney Unearthed Tour - The Common Graves of Abney
- 9th September - 2pm -
View on facebook
2 years ago
Abney Litter Pick - Saturday 11th August 10am
Abney Litter Pick - Saturday 11th August 10am
-
View on facebook
2 years ago
September Visitors' Centre Opening Hours
September Visitors' Centre Opening Hours -
The opening times for the Abney Park Trust Visitors' Centre will be changing for the next 3 weeks. We will be closed on Monday 3rd, Monday 10th and Monday 17th September. We will be open from 10 am
until 4 pm as usual on all other days, including weekends. Drop in for maps of the park, chat to our ...
...
See more
View on facebook
2 years ago
In the Sticks - Summer Holidays Forest School at Abney Park - 30th July - 10th August
In the Sticks - Summer Holidays Forest School at Abney Park - 30th July - 10th August -
We are looking forward to summer at Abney after a fun-filled May half term. We will be running a holiday club for children aged 8 to 13 for two weeks (ages 6-7 are able to join on Thursdays and
Fridays). We will have time to explore the beautiful park , immerse ourselves in the flora and fauna, buil...
...
»
What is a Funeral Plan?
Pages
Get In Touch
Policy
Terms Of Service
